# WENJUN XUE

## JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



## CONTACT



Portnergasse, 12 Regensburg 93047



+49 017 4422-8997



wenjunxue@web.de



GitHub june9999



LinkedIn Wenjun Xue

## **SKILLS**

- Java, Python
- HTML, CSS
- **Javascript**
- React
- NodeJS, Express
- SQL, MongoDB
- Git, Github
- Jira, Trello, Agile
- **Unit Testing**

## **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

C1

German **B2** 

Mandarin Mother tongue

Regensburg August 16, 2023

Wazin Xue

## **ABOUT ME**

Motivated and ambitious junior software engineer/full-stack web developer, dedicated to producing clean, sustainable code. With a solid foundation from bootcamp and university, I excel in JavaScript and Java. Ready to contribute technical expertise and embrace new challenges as I continue to develop professionally.

## **EDUCATION**

05.2023 - 09.2023

### Full-Stack Web & App Bootcamp

WBS Coding School, Berlin

- Focus: honing practical software development skills & fostering a deep understanding of modern web technologies
- · Project: Team projects, including Delivery Web, Movie Web

09.2019 - 09.2022

#### Master of Science in Management

University of Mannheim, Mannheim

- Focus: Information System & Operation
- · Master thesis: Explorative study in transport management applying process mining technology
- Final grade: 1,8

## WORK EXPERIENCE

09.2021 - 05.2022

#### **Thesis Student**

Camelot Management Consultants, Mannheim

- · Conducted data extraction from SAP TMS, digitized processes using BPMN and Process Mining software (Celonis)
- · Wrote gueries in MySQL to combine data for process analysis
- · Defined KPIs, including process variants, throughput time and repeated events
- · Created dashboards for performance tracking

06.2021 - 08.2021

#### **Operation Intern**

SAIC Volkswagen Automotive Company, Shanghai ·Assisted capacity analysis from over 400 suppliers to support production

- · Automated data collection process for reporting with Python
- · Supported team administration, such as contract tracking

## **OTHERS**

Databases and SQL for Data Science with Certificate

Python (IBM)

GMAT (Score: 700)

Games, Bakery, Yoga Hobbys